good evening everybody welcome sit in
2017 awards night great to see you
ladies and gentlemen tonight is a
much-anticipated event as we bestow the
honor to the brilliant people who have
performed and exceeded passionately
to meet their goal and go beyond their
goals in 2016
[Music]
[Applause]
tonight we'll be recognizing and
celebrating our most fantastic
performances from our top achievers all
approver in these rooms and off
[Music]
keep up the fantastic work that you're
doing because if you just keep doing
what we've been doing we'll have another
fantastic year as we grow and move
towards our number five in five objects
[Music]
so 2016 Philippines absolutely agency
which is all of you and more grew by 311
percent in Philippines this 300% growth
and the pace at which we're growing
makes you makes us makes your team the
fastest growing agency in Asia or
[Music]
might have been a great event and it
will continue we have built them some
surprises left for you but I want you to
enjoy the rest of the evening have a lot
of fun SWT go go go go go